<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Specification on</title><link>https://www.wormholeim.org/docs/</link><description>Recent content in Specification on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.wormholeim.org/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://www.wormholeim.org/docs/introduction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wormholeim.org/docs/introduction/</guid><description>How does it work? Intra and Inter Messaging Only inter-app messages go through wormhole server, intra messages will have no difference. We provide client SDKs which help you to integrate with the least effort.
Messaging Restful APIs are provided to register users, create chats and complete with E2EE etc. Websocket provides efficient messaging interface that avoids the overheads of negotiation and reduces the latency. WebRTC is introduced to secure real-time voice and video calls over the web.</description></item><item><title>Client-Server API</title><link>https://www.wormholeim.org/docs/client-server-api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.wormholeim.org/docs/client-server-api/</guid><description>Overview Wormhole server APIs are forked from Synapse Server. We keep most of the APIs and describe the changes below.
Matrix synapse as it describes, is an ambitious new ecosystem for open federated Instant Messaging. However, we believe the need for server-side integration or modification is such a pain. We prefer to provide centralized Chat Server to reduce overhead. For example, if an app already has its own IM service, there’s nothing related to Wormhole.</description></item><item><title>Platform API</title><link>https://www.wormholeim.org/docs/platform-api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.wormholeim.org/docs/platform-api/</guid><description>Almost every APIs are well handled by our native SDKs, there&amp;rsquo;re still APIs that allow your application server to work with accounts and data related to your Wormhole application. The API lets you create accounts, set users' token programmatically so that you can boost your login conversion rate.
Base URL Every application has its unique base url. For now, to join Wormhole and get an app ID, app token, and a base URL, please email to &amp;ldquo;p.</description></item></channel></rss>